If you're looking for it, though, the
politically correct term for me right
now is actually African Latino.
And if you've never heard of that,
basically,
we're like the next big thing.
>> [laughter]
>> Yes. They compare us to Bitcoin in 2011.
It's like,
invest now cuz the stock is going up,
you know?
People didn't even know we were real. We
just came out of nowhere. We're like
unicorns. We just popped up one day out
of nowhere, you know? Talented, triple
threat. We could do it all. Dance,
salsa, speak Spanish, and say the
N-word. So, the opportunities are
endless.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm a proud Hispanic man, though. A lot
of negative stereotypes about Hispanic
men right now. I had a girl tell me she
don't date Hispanic men because they
cheat and they can't commit to a
relationship, but that's a stereotype.
You can't always listen to what other
people say. Like my grandparents, they
just celebrated 59 years of being
together.
>> [cheering]
>> Yeah.
>> [applause]
>> And things are going great.
So, they're thinking about getting
married.
>> [laughter]
>> My grandmother might be the one.